When this is part of your outfit
Today's video is about a topic I haven't shown you before
A latex catsuit with pockets for silicone inserts
This means this video is about a big cat suit
and you can size up your chest
and for this I teamed up with Visage Latex
from which I'm also wearing this beautiful basic dress
I styled the dress with a corset belt and my Swedish collar
collar and bracelets and yes they're always quite noisy but I think that's part of it
from the outside you basically only see cups
and by the way another premiere here it's a 0.4 millimeter neck entry catsuit I've only
one 0.25 millimeter neck entry catsuit so I have to squeeze through this hole here but
let's talk about the cups I think I'm going to turn this inside out to show it to you
okay so we have the neck hole little part here which builds the pockets you need something to
put inside but before I'm going to show you the silicon implants I'm going to change into the
catsuit first I managed to get into it and it wasn't as bad as I thought with a 0.4 millimeter
your neck entry if you want to know how to get into your neck entry catsuit I have a video
for that on my channel and you can check it out and it's basically the same with the 0.4 millimeter
I used an ungodly amount of silicone oil and now here I am and as you may see there's a bit of
loose fit here and I'm going to put these inside
Visage actually recommended to put them inside only after dressing the entire catsuit so I'm
curious how that will work and of course these are the right fit for this catsuit and this cut
so you can't just use any fake boobs but you should check with the manufacturer or shop
and ideally buy the both of them together.
In theory, I'm going to pull away the neck here
and then squeeze the boot inside.
To be honest, I'm going to get help for that.
And I also wanted to show you something else
before I dress the shoes.
Get rid of my cozy.
We have these kind of stirrups here on the feet.
I quite like them because I think it's easier to dress the catsuit if you have this fixed point where to start.
I put one side in so you can see the side by side comparison.
Like this is with the implant and this without.
Yes, no, yes, no, yes.
Basically this is like that.
and what I recommend is putting silicone oil on the fake boob too and then just
gently pushing it down and letting it slide into place and wiggle it a bit so that it
um settles down
both inlays are inside the sit-no and I think the look is spectacular
I have to say this is made to measure and I think it doesn't look like it because it fits so good
there is nothing I could complain about literally it's not too short so the whole back is yeah
in place so there's no space between my spine and the catsuit it's long enough obviously and
the boobs fit the collar fits the crotch area fits really good I just love it it's really
extraordinary from the fit and we have a really intricate cut too there's like this v-shape
insert here which basically has I think it has no function maybe it adds to the good fit but
it really looks nice and also on the back side we have multiple panels here so not
just one back panel but we have these additional panels here which make a great booty too
so yeah i am really happy with the fit and the catsuit there's a lot of reinforcement on
critical places on the inside not only here on the hands but also in the armpits
there are labels inside we have a flap behind the cross zipper so nothing gets
stuck and yeah Visage sells currently via Tmall an Asian platform but they're
working on another web page so you can shop there from everywhere in the world
I will link everything down below if you have any questions concerning shipping
please write them a message and ask them they're really really nice and of course
as always if my idea is good for the catsuit I'm going to add one of my various metal
because they just fit like everything
and I think it's another notch here which elevates the whole look without
taking away too much from the catsuit itself. Alright I hope you enjoyed this
video if you want to see more of this catsuit for example check out my Patreon
and as I said I will link everything in the description text thanks to Visage
Latex for trusting me with this project and sending this to me I really love it
and yeah I am going to have dinner now I wish you a nice day see you in the next
video bye